A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Natural Resources, 1999-2010 (bulk 2006-2009)
Library of Virginia
- I. Correspondence and subject files, 1999-2010 (bulk 2006-2010)., 27.22 cu. ft. (30 boxes)
  - Governor-related, 2006-2009., .7 cu. ft. (2 boxes)
    Contains of correspondence, legislative files and supporting documentation sent between the Secretary of Natural Resources and the Governor, covering special projects initiated by the Governor. Notable projects include the Governor's Year of Energy and Environment as well as the implementation of the American Recovery and Reinvestment Act in Virginia.
    - Governor and his staff, 2007-2009. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Governor and his staff, 2006-2007. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Governor and his staff, 2006. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Executive-generated correspondence for Governor's signature, 2006-2009. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Executive Order 82, 2007-2008. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Governor's Institute Workshops, 2006. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Governor's Year of Energy and Environment, 2009. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Governor's Year of Energy and Environment: Stakeholder Proposals, 2009. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - American Recovery and Reinvestment Act, 2009. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - American Recovery and Reinvestment Act, 2009. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Urban Policy Task Force, 2006. (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Governor's Year of Energy and Environment, 2009. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - American Recovery and Reinvestment Act, 2009. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - American Recovery and Reinvestment Act, 2009. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Urban Policy Task Force, 2006. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- II. Legislative files, 2006-2009., 2.7 cu. ft. (4 boxes)
  Legislative files, 2006-2009, related to bills that were either under the purview of the Secretary of Natural Resources or upon which the Secretary wished to comment. Legislative action summaries include a summary of the bill; a summary of constituents who would be affected; the recommendation of the agency within the Secretary of Natural Resources as to whether the Governor should sign, veto, or amend the bill; and the recommendation of the Secretary as to whether the Governor should sign, veto, or amend the bill. Graveyard bill folders contain legislative action summaries, copies of bills, and other documentation relating to bills that did not pass the General Assembly. Enrolled bill folders contain enrolled bill reviews, which include the recommendations of the agency and the Secretary as to whether the Governor should sign, veto, or amend the bill. Finally, there is information relating to the creation of the Biosolids Expert Panel by the General Assembly and its operation.
  - Legislative Action Summaries: House bills, 2006. (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Action Summaries: House bills, 2006. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Action Summaries: Senate bills, 2006. (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Graveyard: House bills, 2006. (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Graveyard: Senate bills, 2006. (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Enrolled bill reviews: House bills, 2006. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Enrolled bill reviews: Senate bills, 2006. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - House and Senate bills continued, 2006. (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Action Summaries, 2007. (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Legislative Action Summaries: House bills, 2007. (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Legislative Action Summaries: House bills, 2007. (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Legislative Action Summaries: Senate bills, 2007. (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Graveyard: House bills, 2007. (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Graveyard: House bills, 2007. (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Graveyard: Senate bills, 2007. (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Enrolled bill reviews: House bills, 2007. (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Enrolled bill reviews: Senate bills, 2007. (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Legislative Action Summaries: House bills, 2008. (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Action Summaries: House bills, 2008. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Action Summaries: Senate bills, 2008. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Enrolled bill reviews: House bills, 2008. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Enrolled bill reviews: Senate bills, 2008. (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Graveyard: House bills, 2008. (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Graveyard: Senate bills, 2008. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - House and Senate bills continued, 2008. (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Action Summaries: House bills, 2009. (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Legislative Action Summaries: House bills, 2009. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Legislative Action Summaries: House bills, 2009. (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Legislative Action Summaries: Senate bills, 2009. (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Legislative Action Summaries: Senate bills, 2009. (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Enrolled bill reviews: House bills, 2009. (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Enrolled bill reviews: House bills, 2009. (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Enrolled bill reviews: Senate bills, 2009. (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Graveyard: House bills, 2009. (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Graveyard: House bills, 2009. (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Graveyard: Senate bills, 2009. (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - HJR 640: Studying Cleanup of Virginia's Polluted Waters, 2005. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Legislative initiatives, 2007. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Education, 2007. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Subaqueous Land Conveyances, 2007. (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Legislation correspondence, 2008. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Biosolids Expert Panel, 2007-2008. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Biosolids Expert Panel, 2007-2008. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Biosolids Expert Panel, 2007-2008. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Biosolids Expert Panel: Legislator and General Assembly Correspondence, 2007-2008. (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Biosolids Expert Panel: Panel Member Correspondence, 2007-2008. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Biosolids Expert Panel: Working file, 2007-2008. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Biosolids Expert Panel: Working file, 2007-2008. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Biosolids Expert Panel: Working file, 2007-2008. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Education, 2008. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Research related to biosolids, 2009. (Box 34, Folder 6)
- III. Special programs, 2006-2009., .7 cu. ft. (2 boxes)
  Special programs include correspondence and subject files primarily created by Assistant Secretary of Natural Resources Missy Neff and Deputy Secretary of Natural Resources Nikki Rovner. Topics documented include Governor Tim Kaine's 400,000-acre conservation goal, the Governor's Commission on Climate Change and the Sub-Cabinet on Community Investment.
  - Foundation for Virginia's Natural Resources, 2006. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Energy Policy Advisory Council, 2008. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Governor's Forum on Land Conservation in Southern Virginia, 2007. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Governor's 400,000-Acre Conservation Goal: General Correspondence, 2006-2009. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Land Conservation: Planning and progress, 2006-2009. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Land Conservation Foundation Annual Reports, 2005-2008. (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Land Conservation Tax Credits, 2006. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Land Conservation Correspondence, 2006-2007. (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Land Conservation: Potential Projects, 2006-2009. (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Land Conservation: Miscellaneous, 2006-2009. (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Governor's 400,000-Acre Conservation Goal: Large Tracts, 2007-2009. (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Land Conservation: The Forestland Group, 2006. (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Governor's 400,000-Acre Conservation Goal: Local Governments, 2006-2007. (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Governor's Natural Resources Leadership Summit, 2006. (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Natural Resources Summit, 2003-2006. (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - HB1150: Water Clean-up Plan, 2007-2009. (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - HB1150: Water Clean-up Plan, 1999. (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - HB1150: Water Clean-up Plan Stakeholder Comments, 2006-2008. (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - HB1150: Water Clean-up Plan Working File, 2005-2007. (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - HB1150: Water Clean-up Plan Working File, 2006-2007. (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Land Conservation Work Group, 2006. (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Invasive Species Council, 2005-2008. (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Invasive Species Working Group, 2005-2009. (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Cabinet on Community Investment, 2006-2009. (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Cabinet on Community Investment, 2007. (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Cabinet on Community Investment, 2007. (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - George Washington National Forest Management Plan, 2007. (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Governor's 400,000-Acre Conservation Goal: Conferences and Workshops, 2006-2007. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Governor's 400,000-Acre Conservation Goal: Deputy's Working File, 2005-2007. (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Land Conservation Transaction Workshops, 2006. (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Land Conservation: MeadWestVaCo, 2007. (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Green Commonwealth Challenge, 2009. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Land Preservation Tax Credit: Legislation, 2006-2008. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Governor's 400,000-Acre Conservation Goal: Land deals, 2007-2008. (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Land Conservation Tax Credit: VLCF Criteria, 2006-2008. (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Operational Reviews, 2007. (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Stakeholder Workgroup on Transmission Infrastructure and Open Space Conservation, 2008-2009. (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Energy Plan, 2005-2006. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Energy Plan, 2007. (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Office of the Attorney General Agriculture and Environmental Working Group, 2007. (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Governor's Commission on Climate Change: Chairman, 2008. (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Commission on Climate Change: Chairman, 2008. (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Governor's Commission on Climate Change: Chairman, 2008. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Commission on Climate Change: Correspondence and Press Articles, 2008-2009. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Governor's Commission on Climate Change: Correspondence and Press Articles, 2007-2008. (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Governor's Commission on Climate Change: Interim and Final Reports, 2008. (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Commission on Climate Change: Meeting Material, 2008. (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Governor's Commission on Climate Change: Meeting Material, 2008. (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Commission on Climate Change: Meeting Material, 2008. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Commission on Climate Change: Meeting Material, 2008. (Box 40, Folder 2)
- IV. Speeches, 2006-2009., Extent: 1.7 cu ft. (3 boxes)
  Contains speeches given by L. Preston Bryant, Jr., at public and private events. Includes the speech given by L. Preston Bryant, his notes, correspondence about the event, and promotional material relating to the event.
  Chronological.
  - Remarks at VEBA Legislative Day, 2006 January 18. (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Association of Planning District Commissions 2006 Winter Conference, 2006 January 30. (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Historic Preservation Awards, 2006 January 31. (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Seafood Council, 2006 February 8. (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Citizens Advisory Committee Meeting, 2006 February 9. (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Upper Potomac Roundtable Conference, 2006 March 2. (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Chamber Natural Resources Committee, 2006 March 7. (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Water Conference, 2006 March 21. (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Richmond Bar Association Environmental Law Section, 2006 March 17. (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Legacy Museum, 2006 March 28. (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Association of Soil and Water Conservation Districts, 2006 March 29. (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Bellevue School Highway Marker Dedication, 2006 April 3. (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Dairy Conservation Field Day, 2006 April 5. (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Featherfin Wildlife Management Area Dedication, 2006 April 6. (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Downtown Development Association, 2006 April 13. (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Environment Virginia, 2006 April. (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Association of Soil and Water Conservation Districts, 2006 April 24. (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - BikeWalk Virginia, 2006 May 1. (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Water Environment Association, 2006 May 1. (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Virginia Tech Department of Geosciences Graduation, 2006 May 13. (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Virginia Resource Use Education Council, 2006 May 23. (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - First Annual Virginia Restoration Day, 2006 May 31. (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Department of Conservation and Recreation Watershed Management Workshop, 2006 June 8. (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Hopewell Regional WWTF/VEEP Ceremony, 2006 June 13. (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Waste Solutions Forum Steering Committee, 2006 June 15. (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Cycle Systems 25th Anniversary, 2006 June 27. (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - SWANA Annual Meeting, 2006 June 29. (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - United States Army Corps of Engineers Norfolk District Chain of Command Ceremony, 2006 June 30. (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Annual Dinner Meeting of the York Chapter of the Chesapeake Bay Foundation, 2006 July 15. (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - HB1150 Stakeholder Kickoff Events, 2006 July 21. (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Southeastern Equestrian Trails Conference, 2006 August 4. (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Southeastern Public Service Authority Board of Directors, 2006 September 7. (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Remarks at Sorenson, 2006 September 8. (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Governor's Environmental Excellence Award Banquet, 2006 September 13. (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Governor's Natural Resources Summit, 2006 September. (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - HBAV and EarthCraft Home Program, 2006 September 21. (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Virginia Energy Plan Public Listening Session, 2006 September 25. (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Virginia Preservation Council, 2006 September 26. (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Virginia Executive Institute, 2006 September 29. (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Middle Peninsula Land Trust, 2006 October 1. (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Captain John Smith Water Trail Sign Unveiling, 2006 October 2. (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Hunton and Williams' Mission H2O Conference, 2006 October 6. (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - Columbia Gas Remediation Site Celebration, 2006 October 12. (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - Pure H2O Forum, 2006 October 13. (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - Virginia Energy Conference, 2006 October 18. (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - State of the James, 2006 October 19. (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - Chesapeake Bay Conference, 2006 October 20. (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - Senate Agriculture Retreat, 2006 October. (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - Inauguration of Robert Lindgren at Randolph-Macon College, 2006 October 27. (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - Randolph-Macon College Environmental Stewardship Event, 2006 October 29. (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - BP's Donation of 655 Acres to The Nature Conservancy, 2006 October 31. (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - Virginia Energy Plan Public Listening Session, 2006 November 2. (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - Virginia Water Science and Technology Symposium, 2006 November 3. (Box 41, Folder 53)
  - Southeastern Association of Fish and Wildlife Agencies, 2006 November. (Box 41, Folder 54)
  - Naval Academy Conference on the Chesapeake Bay Program, 2006 November. (Box 41, Folder 55)
  - Senate Finance Committee, 2007 January 10. (Box 41, Folder 56)
  - Virginia Natural Resources Leadership Institute, 2007 January 11. (Box 41, Folder 57)
  - House Appropriations Committee, 2007 January 17. (Box 41, Folder 58)
  - Virginia Seafood Council, 2007 January 24. (Box 41, Folder 59)
  - The Environment: Can We Afford It?, 2007 January 29. (Box 41, Folder 60)
  - PISCES Award Presentation to the City of Lynchburg, 2007 February 9. (Box 41, Folder 61)
  - Remarks at Shirley Plantation, 2007 February 22. (Box 41, Folder 62)
  - Virginia Museum of Natural History Gala and Grand Opening, 2007 March. (Box 41, Folder 63)
  - Environment Virginia 2007, 2007 March 12. (Box 41, Folder 64)
  - Virginia Water Conference, 2007 March 13. (Box 41, Folder 65)
  - Remarks at Micron Technology, 2007 March 14. (Box 41, Folder 66)
  - Environment Virginia Symposium, 2007 April 7. (Box 41, Folder 67)
  - Department of Conservation and Recreation Kiosk Event at Staunton River Battlefield, 2007 May 1. (Box 41, Folder 68)
  - Thomas Jefferson Awards: Virginia Museum of Natural History Foundation, 2007 May 2. (Box 41, Folder 69)
  - Water Environment Federation, 2007 May 8. (Box 41, Folder 70)
  - Richmond Urban Land Institute Urban Marketplace Event, 2007 May 9. (Box 41, Folder 71)
  - Hampton Roads Sanitation District Awards Luncheon, 2007 May 17. (Box 41, Folder 72)
  - Philip Morris USA E3 Ceremony, 2007 May 22. (Box 41, Folder 73)
  - VaULT Conference, 2007 June 1. (Box 41, Folder 74)
  - Rice Property Dedication, 2007 June 4. (Box 41, Folder 75)
  - Covanta Presentations to the Secretary of Natural Resources and the Department of Environmental Quality, 2007 June 14. (Box 41, Folder 76)
  - Potomac Supply Corporation Bio-Energy Kilns Announcement, 2007 June 25. (Box 41, Folder 77)
  - Virginia Environmental Stewardship Awards, 2007 June 26. (Box 41, Folder 78)
  - Environmental Protection Agency Visit to Lake Manassas, 2007 July 18. (Box 41, Folder 79)
  - Summit for Volunteer Water Quality Monitoring, 2007 July 21. (Box 41, Folder 80)
  - Potomac Forum V, 2007 August 10. (Box 41, Folder 81)
  - National Wetlands Conference, 2007 August 28. (Box 41, Folder 82)
  - Department of Game and Inland Fisheries Safe Boat PR Event, 2007 August 28. (Box 41, Folder 83)
  - Saltsville Elementary School Virginia Naturally Program, 2007 September 6. (Box 41, Folder 84)
  - Coal Mining and the Aquatic Environment Symposium, 2007 September 6. (Box 41, Folder 85)
  - Virginia Recreation and Parks Society Annual Conference, 2007 September 9. (Box 41, Folder 86)
  - Virginia Society of CPAs, 2007 September 28. (Box 41, Folder 87)
  - Fairfax County Department of Public Works and Environmental Services, 2007 October 13. (Box 41, Folder 88)
  - Big Sandy Interstate Water Quality Agreement, 2007 October 25. (Box 41, Folder 89)
  - Elizabeth River Project Summit, 2007 November 6. (Box 41, Folder 90)
  - Dedication of Tayloe and Helen Murphy Hall, 2007 November 7. (Box 41, Folder 91)
  - Remarks at VACO Annual Conference, 2007 November 12. (Box 41, Folder 92)
  - Wild Turkey Release, 2007 November 13. (Box 41, Folder 93)
  - Commonwealth Poultry MOA Signing, 2007 November 14. (Box 41, Folder 94)
  - Department of Environmental Quality Mercury Symposium, 2007 November 28. (Box 41, Folder 95)
  - DuPont Fabros Technologies Meeting, 2007 December 3. (Box 41, Folder 96)
  - International Air Quality Council Conference, 2007 December 4. (Box 41, Folder 97)
  - Virginia Coastal Zone Partners Workshop, 2007 December 7. (Box 41, Folder 98)
  - Montana Tech-Virginia Tech Research Partnership, 2008 January 9. (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Blue Ridge Gatorade Facility, 2008 February 4. (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Congressional Delegation Briefing, 2008 February 4. (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Aging Infrastructure-The Engineering Challenge of Sustaining the Built Environment, 2008 February 21. (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Remarks at the League of Women Voters, 2008 March 25. (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Environment Virginia, 2008 April. (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Merrimac Farm Dedication, 2008 April 10. (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Local Government Council's Annual Meeting, 2008 April 16. (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Ribbon Cutting at Bethel Landfill, 2008 April 18. (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Public Square on the James River, 2008 May 5. (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Senate Finance Subcommittee Retreat, 2008 May. (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - James River Basin Association, 2008 May 27. (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Invasive Species Working Group, 2008 June 4. (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Greater Richmond Chamber of Commerce June Vision Check, 2008 June 5. (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Civil Rights Memorial Conference Call, 2008 June 5. (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - CNX Gas New Conference, 2008 June 11. (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Governor's Awards for the Arts, 2008 July 9. (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Meeting with Vulcan Materials, 2008 July 14. (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - EarthCraft Reception, 2008 July 22. (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Jefferson Green Homeowners Association, 2008 July 28. (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Department of Conservation and Recreation, 2008 July 29. (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Philip Morris Park 500 VEEP E4 Celebration, 2008 September 2. (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Opening Convocation at Longwood University, 2008 September 11. (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Virginia Economic Developers Association Fall Conference, 2008 September 25. (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Entering A New Era of Transatlantic Climate and Energy Cooperation, 2008 September 30. (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Association for the Preservation of Virginia Antiquities Conference, 2008 October 6. (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Joint Workshop on Climate Change, 2008 October 30. (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Green and Sustainable Building Symposium, 2008 October 31. (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Cabinet on Community Investment, 2008 November 10. (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Electric Cooperatives Luncheon, 2009 January 26. (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - LEAD Hampton Roads Military Day, 2009 March 19. (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Boy Scout Troop 2880 Wild Game Feast, 2009 March 28. (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Environment Virginia, 2009 March-April. (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Environmental Protection Agency and Governor's Announcement about the PISCES Award to Abingdon and $80 million ARRA Clean Water Check, 2009 July 6. (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Wintergreen Crawford's Knob Event, 2009 July 24. (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Tobacco Warehouse District Parking Facility Ribbon-Cutting, 2009 July 30. (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Southern Governor's Association Annual Meeting, 2009 August. (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Stewardship Initiative at the State Fair, 2009 September 2. (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Subcommittee on Water Resources and Environment, 2009 September 22. (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Water Research Conference, 2009 October. (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - News Conference with Senator Cardin, 2009 October 19. (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - CVWMA/Keep Virginia Beautiful Litter Summit, 2009 October 21. (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - James River Green Building Council's Annual Leadership Awards Luncheon, 2009 November 18. (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Conference on Economic Leadership, 2009 December 10. (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2006-2009. (Box 43, Folder 17)